

DHISON MALKI C

ADMINISTRATIVE HR



SUMMARY

Experienced HR professional with 7+ years of administrator experience. Demonstrated skills in managing records, responding to employee questions and providing operational support. Passionate about database management and working with new hires to ensure effective onboarding.



EDUCATION

PONJESLY COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING | Kanyakumari, TN

MBA IN HR 2013-2015

CSI INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY | Thovalai, Kanyakumari, TN

BE (EEE) 2008-2012

GOVERNMENT Hr. Sec. SCHOOL | Boothapandy, Kanyakumari, TN 2007-2008

GOVERNMENT Hr. Sec. SCHOOL | Boothapandy, Kanyakumari, TN 2005-2006

SLSC



EXPERIENCE

Sakthi Engineering Works | Kudankulam, Tamil Nadu. **Electrical Maintainance Supervisor** May 2012-May 2013

Sakthi Engineering Works | Kudankulam, Tamil Nadu. Administrative HR JAN 2015-JULY 2021

Lemuria Martial Arts | Nagercoil, Kanyakumari, Tamil Nadu. Administrative HR Aug 2021- March 2023



CURRENT WORKING

COLLMAN SERVICES | Coimbatore, TN. **Branch Admin HR** May 2023-till date

Recruited and identified promising candidates. Conduct periodic and regular benefit plan evaluations. Review current contracts and ensure communications with all parties throughout the decision process. Administer short-term disability plans, leave of absence, and paid time off for all employees. Request staffing needs from department managers to avoid understaffing. Recommend appropriate training for new hires.



CONTACT ME

malkidhison@gmail.com Email

Phone +916380388443 +919787982490 WhatsApp:

Address : NO:23B/62,RamalingaJothi

> Nagar, Ramanathapuram, Coimbatore 641045



OTHER SKILLS

Maintaining discipline among employees Hard Working Strong Management Skills **System Orientation** Creativity Leadership **Problem Solving**



MS OFFICE WINDOWS OS **AUTOCAD** OUTLOOK **PRESENTATION WEBMAIL**



✓ JOB RESPONSIBILITIES

HR Planning Recruitment & Induction HRIS/MIS **Time Office and Payroll Employee Relations Exit Formalities.**